Contact

7306503438 (Home) palakurthi.anirudh@gmail.co m

www.linkedin.com/in/ anirudhpalakurthi3832 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python

Machine Learning Algorithms

Data Science

Certifications

Oracle Certified Associate, Java SE 7 Programmer

Cambridge English Language Assessment

Python Data Structures

Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python)

Using Git for Distributed Development

Publications
LIZARD-O-PHOBIA

Anirudh palakurthi

Software Development Senior Associate at NTT DATA

Rangareddy, Andhra Pradesh, India

Summary

Experienced Senior Development Associate with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, C++, and Windows. Strong professional with a Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.) focused in Electronics and Communications Engineering from gitam university.

Experience

NTT DATA

Software Development Senior Associate February 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 4 months) Bengaluru Area, India

NTT DATA

Intern

October 2017 - February 2018 (5 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Inovas Tech intern student August 2014 - September 2014 (2 months)

study concepts of C,C++ and build console application for attendance management

Inovas Tech intern student August 2014 - September 2014 (2 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Education

Great Lakes Institute of Management

Post Graduate Program- Data Science Engineering, Data Science · (2019 - 2019)

GITAM University

Bachelor of Technology (B.Tech.), Electronics and Communications Engineering \cdot (2013 - 2017)

Narayana Junior College - India intermediate, Maths,physics,chemistry · (2011 - 2013)

Rao's High School 10 class · (2008 - 2011)